Inspect D
YouTube1 has closed around 59
and it can be seen that it had gone up quite a bit
and then after coming and trusting, it is
seen falling down here and there is a chance that
it will go up again, so I give you a
buy recommendation again and the previous
recommendation has already hit the target, if you
want, you can go and check out the video,
if we talk about today's performance, then
here we can see that
today's performance went down
to 846 and today's high went up
to 1885, if we talk about within one year, the
low here was ₹
353 and the high went up to ₹300, so there is a good
movement here, it can be seen, a
buy recommendation is coming here
from the side of Grow, Grow people have said here that you can
buy at 64, hold at 23 and sell at
14, this is totally from their side,
so I  If I were to give you a recommendation, you
could come and buy it at almost how much. So let's
assume here that you can come and buy at
18800.40. Otherwise,
you can buy at the current market price above the closing price,
around 1800.65. You can come and buy it. It is going to be a buy
and its close will be around
1840. Its close will be till 1840. And the target
is amazing. Come and see the target here. It will be
till 904. The first target and the second
target is
910. Both these targets can be achieved tomorrow if
you want. Just analyze and do
not trade because
if you trade in the beginning, there is a
very high risk of losing money. The
recommendation I am giving is totally up to you whether
you trade or not. If
you trade, do it at your own risk. Otherwise,
just for knowledge, come and
see how the movement is going and
what kind of data is coming. I hope you got some
new information.  If you
want more videos related to share market then you
can subscribe to our channel and by going
inside our channel you will
get many videos with the help of which you
can easily trade in the share market, thank you
for watching this video guys, thank you.